■ About Me

Experience Designer and Full-stack developer with experience in building web apps based on pure JavaScript. Successfully completed multiple unique projects, each one having its own set of accomplished challenges. Love to experiment with modern technologies. Looking forward to starting my journey as a full-stack developer at a company which will not only challenge me but helps me develop my skillset further.

Professional Experience

Web Application Developer, Enlighten Infosystems ☑ Nov 2020 – Apr 2021 | Vadodara, India

- Built modern Web Application with Progressive Web App and JavaScript.
- Composed a real-time Web-App based on certificate verification that gives authority to the officials (University/Institute/Organization) to issue a certificate to the candidate and with many more other functionalities.
- Integrated Progressive Web App and worked for fetching data, animation, and structure offline.
 Firebase used for Database.
- Code available under Vericert 🛮 repository.

Software Intern, Enlighten Infosystems ☑ May 2018 – Jun 2019 | Vadodara, India

- Wrote code on JavaScript using Visual Studio and Firebase.
- Evaluated project requirements & specifications correctly and developed a software application that surpassed the mentor's expectations.
- Code available under FreedomForFashion

 repository.

Projects

Personal Portfolio Website 🗷

Apr 2021

- My personal portfolio website.
- Technology Stack: Gatsby, React.js

REIG, Reminder and Event in Group ☑ May 2018 – Oct 2018

- Web Application based on JavaScript, Pure HTML + CSS + BOOTSTRAP and Progressive Web Apps.
- Online real-time chat, storing, and sharing images and documents with the help of Firebase.
- In addition to this creating Event and Reminder for the user is also integrated.

Bhargav Borse

- Vadodara, India
- bhargavborse4898@gmail.com
- +91 8160606663
- k bhargavborse.app
- github.com/BhargavBorse
- **y** bhargav_borse

Education

Master of Computer Application,

Parul University $\ensuremath{\square}$

2019 - 2021 | Vadodara, India

• CGPA: 8.11

Bachelor of Computer Application,

Navrachana University ☑ 2016 – 2019 | Vadodara, India

• CGPA: 6.68



Frontend Development

JavaScript, React.js, Gatsby, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap

Backend Development

C#, PHP, SQL, NoSQL, Firebase

Misc

GitHub, VS Code, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

Software Development Methodology

Progressive Web App (PWA)

Certificates

- Google Garage | Digital Marketing ♂
- Cisco | Cyber Security
- Cisco | Introduction to IoT ☑
- Cisco | Networking Essentials ♂

Publications

Web Mining, JETIR ☑ 30 Apr 2021